# Dinh Van Chi Axe

Route du Bois 49b, Ecublens, Switzerland

📱+41 78 960 16 50 | 🗷 axeldvc@gmail.com | 👑 April 24th, 1997 | 💣 axeldinh.github.io/ | 🖸 github.com/axeldinh | 🛅 linkedin.com/in/axel-dinh-van-chi/

# Personal Profile

Freshly graduated of EPFL's Computational Science and Engineering Master program, I am a highly skilled and motivated individual with a strong background in mathematics, computer science, and engineering. Through my coursework and research projects, I have developed expertise in a wide range of areas, including deep learning, computer vision and numerical simulations.

### **Education**

### École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne, EPFL

Lausanne, Switzerland

M.Sc. in Computational Science and Engineering

Sep 2020 - Mar 2023

- Student Assistant for the Machine Learning Course in automn 2021.
- Private Teacher in Mathematics and Physics.
- Courses: Deep Learning, Machine Learning, Applied Data Analysis, Image Processing 1, Advanced Numerical Analysis, Numerical Integration of Dynamical Systems, Parallel and High-Performance Computing, Software Engineering

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

**Cusco 11, Restaurant**Lausanne, Switzerland

Restaurant Manager Mar 2023 - Apr 2023

· Team management, waiter during both lunch and dinner shifts.

**Sony Europe B.V.**Stuttgart, Germany

Research Intern in Computational Imaging

Apr 2022 - Sep 2022

- Interpolation of BRDF data for rendering. Doing so, the reflectance properties of isotropic material could be acquired in 5 minutes against 8 hours prior the project.
- · Implementation using Python and C++. For rendering, the Mitsuba 2 and Unreal Engine softwares were used.
- Technical Skills: Python with PyTorch, NumPy, Matplotlib, Pandas, Scikit-learn, C++, OpenGL, Slurm, Ubuntu Linux, Linux tools, Apt, Scripting, Git.
- Soft Skills: Communication, Presentation skills.

# **Projects**

#### **Motion Correction in Cardiac MRIs**

Lausanne, Switzerland

École Polytechnique de Lausanne

Oct 2022 - Mar 2023

- Deep Learning based extraction of Left Ventricles in MRIs.
- Using pure post-processing methods we improved the overall quality of the MRI scans, avoiding redundant uses of MRI scanner, which are both time-consuming and expensive.
- Technical Skills: PyTorch, PyTorch Lightning, WandB, Slurm.
- Soft Skills: Presentation skills, Report writing.

#### **PDE Solving using Deep Learning**

Lausanne, Switzerland

École Polytechnique de Lausanne

Sep 2021 - Feb 2022

- · Implementation of a Variational Physics-Informed Neural Network framework capable of handling imaginary numbers.
- Experiments made on the Helmholtz equation.

#### **Transfer-Learning in Natural Language Processing**

Lausanne, Switzerland

École Polytechnique de Lausanne

Mar 2021 - Jun 2021

- Study of the finetuning of Bert model by freezing 99.9% of its weights.
- Technical Skills: Natural Language Processing, Hugging Face.

### **Mobile Application Development**

Personal Project

- Integration of a finetuned PyTorch NLP model used as a ChatBot which must reply using a predefined answers database.
- Technical Skills: Android Studio, Flutter.

March 22, 2023

Skills

Programming Python (Pandas, PyTorch, NumPy, Scikit-learn, Seaborn, etc...), CUDA, OpenMPI, Matlab, C++, ŁTFX, Slurm, Git, Markdown.

Engineering **Soft Skills**  Simulation of ODEs and PDEs, Linear Algebra and Matrix Theory, Computer Vision, Signal Processing, Statistics.

Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation, Engaging Presentation.

# Interests

I enjoy cooking on my free-time, especially Italian cuisine.

**Sports** 

Coming from a city along the sea, I love to wake board and surf. During my time in Switzerland, I could easily access the mountains

to snowboard.

# **Languages**

**English** Professional proficiency French Native proficiency

MARCH 22, 2023